parked.com 2000-12-06

# Deerfield.com - Leveraging Internet Connectivity

|    
Deerfield.com is firmly committed to protecting the privacy of its customers and those who sample Deerfield.com products. [](https://www.truste.org/validate/5661) Deerfield.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not share, sell, or otherwise distribute the financial or personal information of our customers or those who otherwise provide personal information to sample our products, to any other organizations in any way other than what is disclosed in this document. 

In accordance with [COPPA](http://www.ftc.gov/opa/1999/9910/childfinal.htm), Deerfield.com does not, at any time, knowingly collect information from, or market our products to, children under the age of 13. 

All financial and personal information collected by Deerfield.com is held in the strictest confidentiality. Any information, such as an Email address, billing and shipping addresses, and other contact information, submitted via a download form, purchase form, beta team registration, or newsletter subscription, remains the sole property of Deerfield.com. This information is used to help us process payment and to send registration information to our customers. 

If at any time, for any reason, Deerfield.com has a need to share customer information, all customers will be contacted via Email for their consent. Instances when we would share information would include the discontinuation of a product, in which case Deerfield.com would like to turn over our customer information to allow for better continuity for our customers. 

There are also instances when Deerfield.com will use a "cookie" in order to track Web site usage. These cookies do not collect personal information and are terminated once customers leave the site. 

Deerfield.com also operates SecureCC, a secure transaction site dedicated to completing secure online orders. When a purchase is made, using a credit card, via the Internet, the transaction will be automatically redirected to SecureCC. All of the Privacy policies of Deerfield.com would apply to SecureCC as well. 

SecureCC uses Public Key Infrastructure (PKI) to make the Internet a safe place to do business. This system integrates a number of different technologies to ensure that the information you transmit remains private and confidential. The typical PKI is made up of: 

  * A certificate authority (CA), who issues and verifies digital certificates. These digital certificates contain information about the public keys that shoppers will use. 
  * A registration authority (RA), the entity that acts as a verifier for the CA before a digital certificate goes out to a requestor. One (or more) directory where the certificates, and therefore the public keys as well, are stored. 
  * A system of certificate management 

A company using the PKI system is given a digital certificate. This certificate can automatically tell your browser that the site is a secure and legitimate business. Along with this certificate comes a number of Public Keys. The vendor site gives your computer one of the Public Keys to use during the transaction. Using this Public Key, you are able to send and receive secure information with the vendor by encrypting your data. The real strength of this system is in the Company Key. The vendor has a private key, known only to their system. It is able to decode the information that the Company's Public Keys encrypt. This Company Key is the only tool able to understand the encrypted messages. 

For more details about the security measures on SecureCC, [please visit the SecureCC Web site](http://www.securecc.com/). 

When a purchase is made via the Internet with a credit card, Deerfield.com uses a third party commerce service to verify credit card details. This company is sent the total price of the purchase, the card number and expiration date, and the cardholders name and billing address. All information transmitted to this third party is sent using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. Using this method of information encryption further insures the privacy and security of all our customers. This information is used only to verify the account and clear the transaction. 

To further protect the privacy of our customers, access to information by our employees is restricted within the company. Only select employees with an absolute need to use that information, in order to better serve customers, are able to view any personal details submitted. 

From time to time, Deerfield.com will request more specific information about our customers. This is done in the form of surveys and is completely voluntary. The information gathered in these surveys helps us determine who our customer base is and what their needs are. By compiling this data we can work to improve customer experiences with the company. 

Personal information provided by customers, or those who sample Deerfield.com products, is sometimes used to contact individuals regarding new information about Deerfield.com products. Anyone contacted by Deerfield.com with product information can request to be removed from further updates at any time. To be removed from Deerfield.com's mailing list or to modify your information previously provided, please refer to the Corporate Web site at [http://www.deerfield.com/service/mailing_removal/](http://www.deerfield.com/service/mailing_removal/index.cfm). 

More than anything, Deerfield.com tries to treat its customers as each one of us would like to be treated. We value our privacy and we value yours, too. It is our goal to make your experience with Deerfield.com a safe and positive experience. 

For more information on Deerfield.com's privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at: [privacy@deerfield.com](mailto:%20privacy@deerfield.com) or by calling 517.732.8856. 

|   
---|---
